<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research on Strange Aeons</title>
    <link>https://www.strangeaeons.org/tags/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research on Strange Aeons</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:45:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.strangeaeons.org/tags/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My Research &amp; Writing Process</title>
      <link>https://www.strangeaeons.org/posts/research-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 17:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.strangeaeons.org/posts/research-process/</guid>
      <description>A recent conversation with a student led me to reflect on my approach to research and writing. These notes might prove useful to someone, somewhere, perhaps, as an example of one research flow. I daresay others have their own working methods, but this is one I&amp;rsquo;ve refined over a long period into something that works consistently for me.&#xA;Nearly all of my work involves either thinking and writing. As an academic, these two practices, thinking and reading, revolve around both my own ideas and the published ideas of others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Argumentation Theory: Quick Start</title>
      <link>https://www.strangeaeons.org/posts/argumentation-quick-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 16:49:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.strangeaeons.org/posts/argumentation-quick-start/</guid>
      <description>So you&amp;rsquo;ve decided to do a project or placement that will feature Argumentation Theory and you&amp;rsquo;re wondering where to start. Helping bootstrap your knowledge of Argumentation Theory is the point of this post. I&amp;rsquo;ll likely develop the content over time, as new resources and papers become available, or as my own foci within argumentation changes. I&amp;rsquo;ll also intersperse thrid party resources with, probably reasonable opinionated summaries of specific topies, just so that if we work together, you have an idea of my position on things.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
