<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Admin on Strange Aeons</title>
    <link>https://www.strangeaeons.org/tags/admin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Admin on Strange Aeons</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:51:51 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.strangeaeons.org/tags/admin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contacting Me</title>
      <link>https://www.strangeaeons.org/posts/contacting-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 17:51:51 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.strangeaeons.org/posts/contacting-me/</guid>
      <description>Methods If, as a student, you need to contact me, then please consider the following order of preference for communication methods:&#xA;Timetabled Contact Hours - If I&amp;rsquo;m currently teaching you on a module then the best way to ensure there is time devoted to you is to turn up to the lecture or lab, or both. I&amp;rsquo;ve already got the time put aside for exactly this eventuality. As it is face-to-face then we can efficiently get to the root of the problem and hopefully solve it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Comments on Strange Aeons</title>
      <link>https://www.strangeaeons.org/posts/commenting-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 13:08:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.strangeaeons.org/posts/commenting-policy/</guid>
      <description>This site has no facility for direct comments because I feel that easy, consequence-free, ill-considered, commentary and discussion has coarsened public discussion.&#xA;I think an element of the problem is a mixture of immediacy and anonymity, combined with a pathological tendency in many people towards reactionary anger. If people can react quickly, and in the moment, especially without consequence, then I think people are more likely to, in the best case, use perhaps ill-considered wording, and in the worst case, to fully indulge their worst inclinations.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
